{"data":[{"question":"Before the invention of the printing press, books have been all printed by hand.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"Before","b":"the printing","c":"have been","d":"by","answer":"3","explain":" - Have been-> had been","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"24","subcategorylv2":"23","type":"1"},{"question":"As the Asian economic miracle spreads throughout the Pacific, wage increases everywhere is affecting millions of consumers.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"As","b":"spreads","c":"is","d":"millions","answer":"3","explain":" - Is-> x","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"24","subcategorylv2":"23","type":"1"},{"question":"The surface of the tongue covered with tiny taste buds.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"the","b":"covered","c":"tiny","d":"buds","answer":"2","explain":" - Covered-> is covered","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"24","subcategorylv2":"23","type":"1"},{"question":"Cosmic distance is measured on light-years.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"Cosmic","b":"is","c":"on","d":"years","answer":"3","explain":" - On-> in","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"24","subcategorylv2":"23","type":"1"},{"question":"A million of tourists from all over the world visit New York every day.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"A","b":"of","c":"all over","d":"visit","answer":"2","explain":" - Of-> x","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"24","subcategorylv2":"23","type":"1"},{"question":"Whereas Earth has one moon, planet call Mars has two small ones.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"Whereas","b":"has","c":"call","d":"ones","answer":"3","explain":" - Call-> called","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"24","subcategorylv2":"23","type":"1"},{"question":"An ardent feminist, Margaret Fuller, through her literature, asked that women be given a fairly chance.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"through","b":"that","c":"be","d":"fairly","answer":"4","explain":" - Fairly-> fair","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"24","subcategorylv2":"23","type":"1"},{"question":"No longer is scientific discovery a matter of one person alone working.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"No","b":"is","c":"matter of","d":"alone working","answer":"4","explain":" - Alone working-> working alone","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"24","subcategorylv2":"23","type":"1"},{"question":"The scientific method consists of forming hypotheses, collect data, and testing results.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"scientific","b":"consists of","c":"collect","d":"results","answer":"3","explain":" - Collect-> collecting","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"24","subcategorylv2":"23","type":"1"},{"question":"All data in computer are changed into electronic pulses by an input unit.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"in computer","b":"into","c":"by","d":"unit","answer":"1","explain":" - In computer-> on computer","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"24","subcategorylv2":"23","type":"1"}]}